Alright
Mr. Qin
Hospital files and the origin of old items
have completed the first round of verification
The results
Hospital records, registers, receipts
signatures, photos of old items, and cloud
backup timestamps all corroborate each other
15 years ago, the one who signed and accompanied the rescued
boy was indeed Mrs. Fu
There's also progress on the old files of Qinghe Orphanage
On the same day 15 years ago
Near the old wall of Qinghe, there indeed was
an unidentified boy who was
briefly hospitalized before entering the rescue process
Age, time, location, and the old scar on the left wrist
all highly match the Fu family's
missing person records from back then
The Chairman wishes to proceed
with the final identity verification
Follow the procedure
The Chairman said he won't rush you to meet the Fu family
But he wants to thank Mrs. Fu
You heard him, Fu Huaishan said thank you
No need to thank me, back then I just did
what I thought was right
What if I insist on thanking you
Not as a way of repaying a debt
But as a husband
Mr. Fu, you're getting so smooth with words
It's the truth
If you really are Fu Yanchi
would you feel that
everything now is too rushed
Like our marriage
Are you trying to make decisions for me again